# itsannatopping@gmail.com 603-533-0908

# **Anna Topping**

Hardworking, responsible **Lead Support Engineer** with five years of client and project management experience. Enjoys collaborating with others and coaching teams to reach their highest potential. Not afraid to ask questions. Based in Boston, MA.

# Experience

# Ungork I New York, NY

### Lead Support Engineer | February 2022 - Present

- Recruiting and coaching support engineers to build out my own team and enable others to solve complex problems.
- I use my technical expertise to create and improve processes and focus on increasing efficiency.

#### Senior Support Engineer | July 2021 - February 2022

- I serve as the highest escalation point for technical support issues within the Global Support Services team.
- Maintain a full working knowledge of Ungork's configuration best practices, new features, and platform capabilities.
- Act as an individual contributor through my independent work creating 10 strategic platform monitors in Datadog and updating three generations of onboarding material. I built my management toolkit mentoring associates and a summer intern.

#### Configuration Support Engineer | January 2021 - July 2021

- I worked closely with engineers, client partners, and delivery team to support Unqork built applications through the SDLC cycle.
- Expert in Unqork configuration through both my own research as well as hands on experience creating Unqork built tools for internal and external use. I shared my knowledge with my teammates and those outside of the team who seek our guidance

## Associate Support Engineer | April 2020 - January 2021

- I used my exceptional problem solving and strong interpersonal communication skills to work with customers and to help resolve their complex Unqork problems.
- I worked directly with over 20 high profile clients including Principal Life, Liberty Mutual, and The City of New York.

# Zero-In I New York, NY

#### Web Project Manager | January 2020 - April 2020

- I worked directly with full stack developers to create new digital marketing solutions for over 50 projects and managed API connections to business management softwares like MindBody, as well as integrations with social media platforms like Instagram and Facebook.
- Managed the entire life 3 high-profile web-based projects with Equinox by communicating with hardware teams, designers, and front end developers.

#### Digital Account Manager | September 2018 - December 2019

- Manager of 73 mid-size accounts, I led weekly project-update meetings, assessed new content requests, and placated support issues and installation requests.
- Oversaw the workflow for over 30 projects at a time by organizing requirements, timelines, and scope. I worked directly with clients to onboard users to CMS systems and provided excellent customer service with frequent reach outs and check-in video calls.

# Education

# General Assembly I New York, NY

Javascript Development I Jan 2020 - April 2020

Mastered the fundamentals of JavaScript and advanced APIs to build a full-functional mobile application.

### Emmanuel College I Boston, MA I Class of 2017

Bachelor of Arts in English, Communications, and Media Studies

#### Javascript and · Amazon Web Datadog A logical Strong Skills jQuery Services approach to communication MongoDB work Linux Cloud Database Confident · Attention to Computing technical trainer · Testing and System detail JIRA and AGILE debugging Management • SQL